The final frontier is only the beginning
The Captains is a documentary, science fiction film directed by William Shatner.
The Captains is a feature-length documentary film
written and directed by William Shatner.
The film follows Shatner as he interviews the other actors who have
portrayed starship captains in the Star Trek franchise.
Himself, played by William Shatner.
Himself, played by Patrick Stewart.
Himself, played by Avery Brooks.
Herself, played by Kate Mulgrew.
Himself, played by Scott Bakula.
Himself, played by Chris Pine.
The Captains is a 2011 feature documentary that follows actor William Shatner through interviews with the other
actors who have portrayed starship captains in five other incarnations of the Star Trek franchise.
Shatner's subjects discuss their lives and careers before,
during, and after their tenure with Star Trek.
They explore the pressures, stigmas, and sacrifices that
accompanied their roles and their larger careers.
The film makes use of conversations, personal
observations, interviews, and archival footage.
The tone is thought_provoking.